Xuan Cuong Ho

Blockchain Engineer

Email : cuong1181998@gmail.com Mobile : +84-35-773-5333

Github: github/cuong1181998 Linked In: linkedin/cuonghx110898 Blog: https://0xcuonghx.netlify.app/

ABOUT

I'm a full-stack developer with many years of experience in Web Development since 2018, mostly using Javascript. Now I develop and researching the EVM-compatible ecosystem.

I have good understanding at fundamental of computer science Data structure and Algorithms, Programming Paradigm, Cryptography, Database Design, etc

I have problem-solving skills and can work independently or in teamwork.

I'm looking for challenging jobs, learning new technology to solve problems.

EDUCATION

• Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Engineer of Information Technology; GPA: 3.03

Hanoi, Vietnam

Sep. 2016 - May. 2021

EXPERIENCE

• G.U Technologies Blockchain Engineer

Remote, Japan Mar 2022 - Present

o Smart contract developer: ERC20, ERC721, etc

- o Building dapps based on EVM-compatible chain: NFT marketplace, NFT bridge, etc
- o Building related tools, SDK: Wallet Connector, etc
- o Skills: Solidity, React, Next.js, The Graph, NestJS

• FPT Telecom International

Hanoi, Vietnam

Apr 2021 - Feb 2022

- Web developer: Building a live-stream platform combined with a sale management system
- o Skills: Nodejs, Apache Kafka, NestJS, React.js, MongoDB, Microservices

• ICTS custom software

Hanoi, Vietnam

Software Engineer

Software Engineer

Aug 2020 - Apr 2021

- Web developer: Outsourcing base on requirements
- o Skills: NestJS, React.js

• FPT Telecom International

Hanoi, Vietnam

Apr 2019 - Aug 2020

- Web developer: Building enterprise management system on web service
- o Skills: React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Microservices

Projects

Intern

- NFT marketplace: Market platform buy and sell NFT on EVM-compatible chain.
- NFT marketplace: Platform bridging NFT on between two EVM-compatible chains.
- Livestream e-commerce: Platform live stream and sell products combine with sale management, shipping.
- Enterprise management system: Microservice support enterprise management system such as IAM, CRM, Booking, etc
- Receipt management base on ORC: Platform allow user capture receipt and manage monthly budget
- Information Retrieval: Build crawler and search engine base on Solr

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- Programing Languages: Javascript, Solidity
- Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Postgresql
- Protocol: RestFul, GraphQl, Socket, MessageQueue
- Software Architecture: Microservice, MVC
- Framework: ReactJS, NextJS, NextJS, SocketIO, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ
- Services: The Graph

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

English: Professional working proficiencyVietnamese: Native or bilingual proficiency

AWARDS

• Mathematics competition in Vinh City in 2013